

ENGINEERING GRADUATE · FULL STACK DEVELOPER · CODING HOBBYIST

159 Yorkland Street, Richmond Hill, ON, Canada, L4S1C5

□ (647) 621-6600 | susean17@my.yorku.ca | seans98 | seansu98

About

An electrical engineering graduate with 1 year of software development experience and a strong aptitude to learn. Seeking entry level software engineering/development positions

Skills

Front-End Development ReactJS (Redux, MaterialUI), HTML, JavaScript (Vanilla, JQuery), CSS (Bootstrap) **Back-End Development** Node.js/ExpressJS, EJS, Python (functional and object-oriented), RESTful APIs

Database Development SQL (MySQL), NoSQL (MongoDB, Mongoose)

QA and Testing Postman **Version Control** Github

Other Languages C, C++, Java, Bash, Verilog, VHDL

Spoken Languages Spanish (Intermediate), English (native)

Projects_

Web-Based Energy Management System

Toronto, Canada Sept 2020 - April 2021

ENGINEERING CAPSTONE (ENG 4000)

Quality Assurance Lead and Backend engineer for developing a web-based energy management system (EMS)

- Collaborated with a team of engineering students in creating an extensive Python simulation, which simulates several energy systems including Battery-Energy Storage Systems, Multi-Unit Residential Buildings, and EV chargers + their car-flow
- Created a backend Python cost calculator that projects future costs for EV charging costs, inputs such as inflation, vehicle maintenance and electricity cost trends were considered
- Debugged code and stress tested the simulation using Postman

Doorbell Project Toronto, Canada

EMBEDDED SYSTEM (EECS 3215)

January 2020 - April 2020

- Created a Doorbell with a remote chime using the LPC 802 Microcontroller for the Embedded Systems term project
- The project contained two sensors and two actuators for input/output
- Programmed the Microcontroller in C for functionality and connections to external peripherals

Work Experience ____

Quality Assurance Co-op Student

Mississauga, Canada

April 2016 - August 2018

CERTAINTEED GYPSUM

April 2019 - August 2019

- Maintained the backend of the Quality Index Database (QI) using Microsoft Access
- Collaborated with managers and leads to restructure web drivers for the company
- Created Standard Operating Procedures (SOP's) outlining the features of the QI Database
- Created weekly quality index reports

Rides Operator Vaughan, Canada

Canada's Wonderland

• Operated rides in a safe and guick manner

- Operated fides in a sale and quick manner
- · Performed daily maintenance checks on rides
- Collaborated with fellow crew members to ensure guest safety and satisfaction
- Attended to guest needs to ensure park enjoyment

Education

Bachelor of Engineering (BEng) in Electrical Engineering

Toronto, Canada

LASSONDE SCHOOL OF ENGINEERING, YORK UNIVERSITY

Expected June 2021

JULY 26, 2021 SEAN SU · RÉSUMÉ